[{"answer": "Well, certainly the debate was a defining moment in this campaign, but I think it's pretty simple.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "I think, you know, two observations on that, Piers.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Do you think the debate performance has actually carried over weight with women generally?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "A number of key differences.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "I mean can you articulate for me exactly what the key difference would be, if he became president?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "Israel is not more secure and Iran is closer to a nuclear weapon.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "So presumably you would like to see -- would you like to see Mubarak?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "Well, what I would want -- well, let -- what I would want and what we didn't have and what we don't have is I'd like to have a strategy.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "I mean where would you go with this threat?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "I think the most interesting thing about Governor Romney is not just this speech but his entire foreign policy approach is the complete absence of specifics and we even heard that from former Senator Coleman there, so he's upset about the situation in Syria.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "What would you say to that?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "It was a fairly dismal performance, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Well, it's not catastrophic.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "This is catastrophic, isn't it?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "We are.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "Are you correcting your prediction?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "If Romney can?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "Well, in the debate he was able to reposition himself toward the center of the electorate.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "So I don't think it's about personality as you said earlier.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "I mean you must be, I would imagine, jubilant at some of these poll numbers today but in reality, can they hold and what is going on with women voters here, do you think?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "I think it's less about the differences in what goals or ultimate vision the two men have, and it's a difference in how they would want to execute them.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Because if he's not, isn't he just talking a lot of hot air?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "Look, I think Mitt Romney's foreign policy can be described like this.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "What does that mean?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "I feel that it's about time, the time that all this commotion was happening, we were forced to leave our home.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "Why do you want to talk out now?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "At that moment it feel like I couldn't believe what had happened.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "What went through your mind in that moment?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "I believe in the judicial system.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "Have you -- have you come to terms with the possibility that George may go to prison for 25 or 30 years if he's found guilty?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "Mr. Morgan, there are so many things that we, you know, can wish as parents, but I will not answer to that question because I don't want, you know, people to elaborate of what, you know, the mother has said.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Do you -- as his mother, do you wish that George had never gone out carrying a gun that evening?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "It was already said by a statement that my son had made public.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "If you had the chance, Gladys, to talk to Trayvon Martin's parents, what would you say to them?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "That I'm deeply sorry for what had happened.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "What would you say as a mother to another mother who had lost her son?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "Well, he's not incarcerated right now.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "How is George doing now, how is he coping with incarceration, how is he coping with the impending trial?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "That's right, that's exactly right, it is restrictive.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "I mean how free is he to go about?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Mr. Morgan, I don't want to touch anything that has to do directly with the case.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "If the situation had been reversed, if it had been George who was going back to visit a family relative, having gone to a store who was unarmed, and he got into an altercation with somebody, Trayvon Martin, for argument's sake, and Trayvon Martin had produced a gun and shot your son dead, do you think you would feel differently about what happened?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "It -- excuse me.", "docId": "121008pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Do you think that regardless of what happens in this case, would you like to see tougher gun control laws in America?", "qSentId": 564}]